Preliminary Guide to the Africa News Service (Durham, N.C.) Leroy T. Walker Africa News Service Archive, 1952-1998 and undated (bulk 1952-1994)
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Corporations (Box 342)
  - "F" (Box 347)
    - Federale (Box 347)
    - Fiat (Box 347)
    - Financial General Bankshares (Box 347)
    - Finansbank Limited (Box 347)
    - Firestone (Box 347)
    - Firestone in Liberia (Box 347)
    - First Bank System (Box 347)
    - First National Bank-Chicago (Box 347)
    - First City Bancorporation of Texas, Incorporated (Box 347)
    - First National City Bank (Box 347)
    - First Pennsylvania Corporation (Box 347)
    - Fisher-Price (Box 347)
    - Florida Power & Light Company (FPL) (Box 347)
    - Flour Corporation (Box 347)
    - Flying Tiger International (Box 347)
    - FMC Corporation (Box 347)
    - Foote, Cone & Belding Communications, Incorporated (Box 347)
    - Foote Mineral Comapny (Box 347)
    - Forbes (Box 347)
    - Ford Motor Company (Box 348)
      - South Africa (Box 348)
    - Fowler (Box 348)
    - Foxboro (Box 348)
    - Frame Group (Box 348)
    - Franklin Electric (Box 348)
    - Freight Services Holding (Box 348)
    - Fuller Company (Box 348)
  - "G" (Box 348)
    - Galion (Box 348)
    - Gardener Denver (Box 348)
    - GAF-General Alliance and Film Corporation (Box 348)
    - G.E.C.-English Electric First Elec. (Box 348)
    - General Dynamics (Box 348)
    - General Electric (Box 348)
    - General Foods (Box 348)
    - General Mining Group (Box 348)
    - General Motors (Box 348)
      - CIC/SA (Box 348)
      - South Africa, 1967-1994, (4 folders) (Box 348)
    - General Telephone (Box 349)
    - General Tire and Rubber Company (Box 349)
    - Gerber-Goldschmidt Group (Box 349)
    - Getty Oil Company (Box 349)
    - Gillette (Box 349)
    - Globe Aero (Box 349)
    - Gold Kist (Box 349)
    - Goldman-Sachs (Box 349)
    - Goldfields (Box 349)
      - Black Mountain (Box 349)
    - Goodrich (Box 349)
    - Goodyear Tire Corporation (Box 349)
    - W.R. Grace (Box 349)
    - Grindlay's (Box 349)
    - Grindrod Intralink (Box 349)
    - Grumman (Box 349)
    - Gulf Oil (Box 349)
      - Angola, thru 1969, 1970-1983, (15 folders) (Box 349)
      - General, 1971-1977, 1981-1985, (7 folders) (Box 349)
    - Gulf & Western (Box 349)
  - "H" (Box 350)
    - Haggie Rand (Box 350)
    - Halliburton Company (Box 350)
    - Hanna Mining (Box 350)
    - Hanes (Box 350)
    - Harper & Row (Box 350)
    - Harris Corporation (Box 350)
    - Harsco Corporation (Box 350)
    - Hatteras Income Securities, Incorporated (Box 350)
    - Hawker Siddeley Electric Africa (Box 350)
    - Heinz (Box 350)
    - Henkel South Africa (PTY) (Box 350)
    - Hercules (Box 350)
    - Hertz (Box 350)
    - Hewlett-Packard (PTY. LTD. Braamfontein, TVL. S.A.) (Box 350)
    - H.H. Roberston Company (Box 350)
    - Highveld Steel & Vanadium (Box 350)
    - Hill and Knowlton, Incorporated (Box 350)
    - Hill Samuel Group (Box 350)
    - Hiram Walker-Gooderham & Worts Ltd. (Box 350)
    - Hitachi (Box 350)
    - Hoechst (Box 350)
    - Holiday Inn (Box 350)
    - Home Security Life (Box 350)
    - Honeywell (Box 350)
    - Hongkong and Shanghai Banking Corporation (Box 350)
    - Hoover (Box 350)
    - Howard Hughes-Corps. Incorporated (Box 350)
    - Hudson Bay Company (Box 350)
    - Hulett's (Box 350)
    - H.L. Hunt Incorporated (Box 350)
    - Hyatt International Corporation (Box 350)
  - "I" (Box 350)
    - IBM (International Business Machine), thru 1974, 1975-89, (4 folders) (Box 350)
      - in South Africa, thru 1971, 1972-92, (5 folders) (Box 350)
    - ICI (see also AE & CI) (Box 351)
    - IDC (Box 351)
    - ILG Industries Incorporated (Box 351)
    - Illings (Box 351)
    - Impala Platinum (Box 351)
    - Imperial Group Ltd. (Box 351)
    - Inco Limited (Box 351)
    - Ingersoll Rand (Box 351)
    - Inland Steel (Box 351)
    - Insurance Company of North American (INA) (Box 351)
    - International Basic Economy Organization (Box 351)
    - International Computers Ltd. (I.C.L.) (Box 351)
    - International Nickel Company (Box 351)
    - International Harvester (Box 351)
    - International Paper (Box 351)
    - International Reporting Information Systems (IRIS) (Box 351)
    - International Signal and Control (Box 351)
    - Interpublic Group of Companies (Box 351)
    - IPI (In the Public Interest) (Box 351)
    - Investors Diversified Services (IDS) (Box 351)
    - Investors Overseas Service (IOS) (Box 351)
    - Irvine Company (Box 351)
    - ISCOR (Box 351)
      - Iron & Steel Corp. ISCOR (Box 351)
    - ITT, 1968-1985 (Box 351)
      - South Africa (Box 351)
  - "J" (Box 351)
    - J. Walter Thompson Company (Box 351)
    - Johannesburg Consolidated Investment (Box 351)
    - John Deere (Box 351)
    - Joseph E. Seagram & Sons (Box 351)
    - Joy Manuf Company (Box 351)
    - J.P. Morgan & Company (Box 351)
    - J.P. Stevens & Company (Box 351)
  - "K" (Box 351)
    - Kaiser (Box 351)
    - Kellogg (Box 351)
    - Kennecott (Box 351)
    - Kidder, Peabody (Box 351)
    - Kimberly Clark (Box 351)
    - King (Box 351)
    - Klockner-Humbold-Deutz (Box 351)
    - Knight-Ridder (Box 351)
    - Kohler Bros. (Box 351)
    - Kopper (Box 351)
    - Kuhn, Loeb (Box 351)
  - "L" (Box 352)
    - Ladd Petroleum Corporation (Box 352)
    - Lauflumenite (Thompson Rmaco Included) (Box 352)
    - Lear Siegler (Box 352)
    - Lehman Brothers (Box 352)
    - Le Monde (Box 352)
    - Lengro Property Organisation (Box 352)
    - Leyland (BMC) (Box 352)
    - Libby-Owens Ford (L.O.F.) (Box 352)
    - Ligget & Myers (Box 352)
    - Lilly (Box 352)
    - Lion Match (Box 352)
    - Lisnave Industry (Box 352)
    - Arthur D. Little (Box 352)
    - Litton Industries, Hewit-Robins-Denver (Box 352)
    - Lloyds Bank (Box 352)
    - Lockheed Aircraft Corporation (Box 352)
      - South Africa (Box 352)
    - Loeb Rhoddes and Company (Box 352)
    - Loew (Lorillard) (Box 352)
    - London Multination Bank (Box 352)
    - Lonrho, through 1977, 1978-1993, (4 folders) (Box 352)
    - Louis Luyt Breweries (Box 352)
    - Loral (Box 352)
    - LTA Limited Group (Box 352)
    - LTV Corporation (Box 352)
  - "M" (Box 352)
    - MCI (Box 352)
    - Macrod (McCarthy-Rolway) (Box 352)
    - McDonnell Douglas (Box 352)
    - Magnavox (Box 352)
    - Manufacturers Hanover Trust Company (Box 352)
    - Marathon Oil Company (Box 352)
    - Marcona Corporation (Box 352)
    - Marie Midland Bank (Box 352)
    - Marley (Box 352)
    - Marvin Josephson Associates (Box 352)
    - Maryland National Bank (Box 352)
    - Massey Ferguson (Box 352)
    - Maosnite Corporation (Box 352)
    - Matrix Company (Box 352)
    - Matsushita Electric Company (Box 352)
    - Maytag (Box 352)
    - Max Factor (Box 352)
    - McDonald's Corporation (Box 352)
    - McGraw-Hill (CI/SA) (Box 352)
    - McKinnon Chain (Box 352)
    - Mead Corporation (Box 352)
    - Mellon National Corporation (Box 352)
    - Mercabank Limited (Box 352)
    - Mercedes Benz (Box 352)
    - Merck, Sharp & Dohme (Box 352)
    - Merril Lynch (Box 352)
    - Messina (Box 352)
    - Metal Box (Box 352)
    - MGM (Box 352)
    - Michelin (Box 352)
    - Middle Witwatersrand (Box 352)
    - Midland Bank (Box 352)
    - Minnesota Mining and Manufacturing (Box 352)
    - Mitre Corporation (Box 352)
    - Mitsubishi Aircraft (Box 352)
    - Mitsui (Box 352)
    - Mobil (Box 352)
      - Clippings (Box 352)
      - Documents I (Box 352)
      - Documents II (Box 353)
      - Rhodesia (Box 353)
    - Molenarr, Incoporated (Box 353)
    - Molycorp, Incorporated (Box 353)
    - Monsanto (Box 353)
      - (CIC/SA) (Box 353)
    - Montedison (Box 353)
    - Moore-McCormack Lines (Box 353)
    - Montecatini of Italy (Box 353)
    - Morgan Guaranty Trust Company (Box 353)
    - Morgan-Stanley Company (Box 353)
    - Morrison-Knudsen (Box 353)
    - Motorola (Box 353)
    - Murphy Oil (Box 353)
    - Murry and Stewart (Box 353)
  - "N" (Box 353)
    - Nabisco (Box 353)
    - Nampak (Box 353)
    - Nashua Corporation of America (Box 353)
    - National Bulk Carriers (Box 353)
    - National Cash Register (Box 353)
    - National Motor Assemblies (Renault Peugeot) (Box 353)
    - National Security Agency (NSA) (Box 353)
    - NCNB (North Carolina National Bank) (Box 353)
      - NCNB, 1977-1986, (2 folders) (Box 353)
      - NCNB, South Africa (Box 353)
    - NCR (Box 353)
      - East Africa (Box 353)
    - Nedbank (Box 353)
    - Nello Teer (Box 353)
    - Nestle (Box 353)
    - Newmont Mining Corporation (Box 353)
    - New Republic Bank (India) (Box 353)
    - Nieman Foundation (Box 353)
    - Nippon Mining Corporation (Box 353)
    - Nord Resources (Box 353)
    - North Carolina Mutual Life (Box 353)
    - Northern States Power Company (Box 353)
    - Northrop Corporation (Box 353)
    - Northwestern Mutual Life Insurance Company (Box 353)
    - Norton Abrasives (Box 353)
  - "O" (Box 353)
    - Oamites Mining (Box 353)
    - Occidental Petroleum (Box 353)
    - Oerlikon (Box 353)
    - Olin Mathieson (Box 353)
    - Olivetti (Box 353)
    - Olympic Airways (Box 353)
    - O'Kiep Copper Company (Box 353)
    - Oppenheimer & Company (Box 353)
    - Orion Banking Group (Box 353)
    - Oshkosh (Box 353)
    - Otis (Box 353)
    - Otrag (Box 353)
    - Ovenstone (Box 353)
    - Overseas Private Investment Company (Box 353)
    - Owens-Corning Fiberglass Company of the U.S. (Box 353)
    - Ownes-Illinois-CIC/SA (Box 353)
  - "P" (Box 354)
    - Page Airways (Box 354)
    - Paine, Webber, Jackson & Curtis (Box 354)
    - Palabora Mining Company (Box 354)
    - Pan Africa Air (CIA) (Box 354)
    - Pan Am (Box 354)
    - Panax Corporation (Box 354)
    - Paribas (Box 354)
    - Parker Pen Company (Box 354)
    - Patterson Publishing Company (Box 354)
    - Paul, Weiss, Rifkind Wharton and Garrison (Box 354)
    - Peat Marwick (Box 354)
    - Pechiney (Box 354)
    - Penguin (Box 354)
    - Pepsi-Cola Corporation (Box 354)
    - Perkins Esquire (Box 354)
    - Petrangol (Box 354)
    - Petro Consulats SA (Box 354)
    - Pfizer (Box 354)
    - Phelps Dodge (Box 354)
    - Phibro (Box 354)
    - Philips (Box 354)
    - Philip Morris (Box 354)
    - Phillips Petroleum Company (Box 354)
    - Phosphate Development Corporation (Box 354)
    - Pick N Pay (Box 354)
    - Pilkington (Box 354)
    - Pilot Radio (Box 354)
    - Pinkerton (Box 354)
    - Piper Aircraft (Box 354)
    - Plate Glass & Shatterprufe Industries (Box 354)
    - Plessey (Box 354)
    - Polaroid In South Africa, 1970-1983, (6 folders) (Box 354)
    - Powell Duffryn (Box 354)
    - Precision Valve (Box 354)
    - Premier Milling (Box 354)
    - Price Waterhouse (Box 354)
    - Prieska Copper Mines (Box 354)
    - Private Export Funding Corporation (PEFCO) (Box 354)
    - Proctor and Gamble (Box 354)
    - Protea (Box 354)
    - Profile Enterprises (Box 354)
    - Prudential (Box 354)
    - Pullman (Box 354)
    - Purex Corporation (Box 354)
  - "R" (Box 354)
    - Rand Carbide (Box 354)
    - Rand Corp (Box 354)
    - Rand Selection (Box 354)
    - Rand Mines (Box 354)
    - Ranger Air (Box 354)
    - Rank Xerox (Box 354)
    - Raytheon (Box 354)
    - RCA (Box 354)
    - Reader's Digest (Box 354)
    - Reed International (Box 354)
    - Renault (Box 354)
    - Rennies Consolidated Holdings (Box 354)
    - Republic Steel (Box 354)
    - Revlon (Box 354)
    - Rex Coulson Mining Services (Box 354)
    - Reynolds (R.J.) (Box 354)
    - Rhodesia Nickel Corporation (Box 354)
    - Rhodesian Acceptances LImited (Box 354)
    - Rhodesian Breweries Limited (Box 354)
    - Rice Council for Market Development (Box 354)
    - Richard Bay Minerals (Box 354)
    - Richardson-Merrell (Box 355)
    - Riggs National Bank (Box 355)
    - Rio Tinto Zinc (Box 355)
    - Roan Consolidated Mines (Box 355)
    - Rockwell International (Box 355)
    - Rohm and Haas (Box 355)
    - Rohr Industries (Box 355)
    - Rolls-Royce (Box 355)
    - Rossing Uranium (Box 355)
    - Rothschilds (Box 355)
    - Rothchild Intercontinental Bank (Box 355)
    - Rupert, Rembrand, Rothmans (Box 355)
    - Rustenburg Platinum Mines, Ltd. (Box 355)
  - "S" (Box 355)
    - Sabs (Box 355)
    - Safair & Safmarine (Box 355)
    - Salomon Bros. (Box 355)
    - Salton Incorporated (Box 355)
    - Sanlam Corporation (Box 355)
    - Santam Bank Limited (Box 355)
    - Sappi (Box 355)
    - Sara Lee (Box 355)
    - Sasbank (Box 355)
    - Sasol, thru 1978, 1979-85, (3 folders) (Box 355)
    - Schlesinger Insurance & Institutional Holdings (Box 355)
    - Joseph Schlitz Brewing Company (Box 355)
    - Seagram Company Ltd. (Box 355)
    - Searle (Box 355)
    - Senatrachem (Box 355)
    - Shearman & Sterling (Box 355)
    - Sheraton Hotels & Inn (Box 355)
    - Shell & B.P. (Box 355)
    - Shell Boycott (Box 355)
    - Shulton Africa (Box 355)
    - Siemens (Box 355)
    - Sigma Motor Corporation (Box 355)
    - Silicon Smelters (Box 355)
    - Singeri (Friden) (Box 355)
    - Skelly Oil Company (Box 355)
    - Slater Walken (Box 355)
    - Smith Corona (Box 355)
    - Societe Generale (Box 355)
    - Societe Nationale of Aquitane (Box 355)
    - Sony Corporation (Box 355)
    - South African Airways/Railways (Box 355)
    - South African Breweries (Box 355)
    - South African Pulp & Paper Ind. Ltd. (Box 355)
    - S.A. Reserve Bank (Box 355)
    - South West Africa Company (Box 356)
    - Southern Company (Box 356)
    - Southern Sun (Box 356)
    - Southern Sun Hotel (Box 356)
    - Space Research Corporation General, thru 1980, 1983-90, (2 folders) (Box 356)
    - Standard Bank (Box 356)
    - Standard Chartered's Corps (Box 356)
    - Sperry Rand--UNIVAC (Box 356)
    - Squibb (Box 356)
    - Standard Bank (Box 356)
    - Standard Oil of California (Box 356)
    - Standard Oil of Ohio (Box 356)
    - Standard & Poor's Corporation, (2 folders) (Box 356)
    - STC's Data Systems (Box 356)
    - Stell & Engineering Industries Federation (SEIFSA) (Box 356)
    - Stephens Inc. (Box 356)
    - Stewart and Lloyds (Box 356)
    - St. Joe Mineral Corporation (Box 356)
    - St. Regis Paper (Box 356)
    - Sulzer Bros.--Rice & Diethelm Ltd. (Box 356)
    - Sumitomo (Box 356)
    - Sumitomo Trust & Banking Co., Ltd. (Box 356)
    - Sun Oil Company (Box 356)
    - Superior Oil (Box 356)
    - Swift (Box 356)
    - Swissair (Box 356)
    - Swiss Bank Corporation (Box 356)
  - "T" (Box 356)
    - T.A. Group (Box 356)
    - Corp. Tadiran (Box 356)
    - Taiyo Kobe Bank, Ltd. (Box 356)
    - Tanganyika Concessions (Box 356)
    - Tate and Lyle (Box 356)
    - TAW International Leasing, Inc. (Box 356)
    - TECNIP (Box 356)
    - Teldelex (Box 356)
    - Telenet (Box 356)
    - Telex (Box 356)
    - Tenneco Incorporated (Box 356)
    - Tennessee Valley Authority (Box 356)
    - Tesoro (Box 356)
    - Texaco (2 corporations) (Box 356)
    - Texas Eastern Corporation (Box 356)
    - Texas Instruments (Box 356)
    - Texas Nuclear Corporation (Box 356)
    - Textron (Box 356)
    - Tiger International, Inc. (Box 356)
    - Time, Inc. (Box 356)
    - Timken (Box 356)
    - T.J. Holt & Company (Box 356)
    - Tongaat Group Limited (Box 356)
    - Top Level International (Box 356)
    - Total (Box 356)
    - Michael J. Twomey PB1663 (Box 356)
    - Toyoto--Wessels (Box 356)
    - Trans-Atlantic Pipeline, Ltd. (Box 356)
    - Trek/Trek Beleggings (Box 356)
    - Triomf Fertilisers (Box 356)
    - Trust Bank (Box 356)
    - The Tsumeb Corporation (Box 357)
    - TCL (Box 357)
    - C.Y. Tung (Box 357)
    - TWA (Box 357)
  - "U" (Box 357)
    - Ucar Minerals (Box 357)
    - UDC Bank Limited (Box 357)
    - Unilever (Box 357)
    - Union Acceptances (Box 357)
    - Union Corporation (Box 357)
    - Union Miniere (Box 357)
    - United Brands (Box 357)
    - United Nuclear (Box 357)
    - Union Carbide, thru 1977, 1978- (Box 357)
    - Union Corporation (Box 357)
    - Union Steel (Box 357)
    - Uniroyal Pty. Ltd. (Box 357)
    - United Airlines (Box 357)
    - United Fruit (Box 357)
    - United Technologies (Box 357)
    - Univac (Box 357)
    - U.S. National Bank of San Diego (Box 357)
    - U.S. Steel (Box 357)
    - U.S. Trust (Box 357)
  - "V" (Box 357)
    - Vinell Corp. (Box 357)
    - Voest-Alpine Corps (Box 357)
    - Volkskas (Box 357)
    - Volkswagen (Box 357)
    - Volvo (Box 357)
    - Vulcan Materials (Box 357)
  - "W" (Box 357)
    - Wachovia Campaign--SAC/s (Box 357)
    - Wachovia (Box 357)
    - Wachovia Bank and Trust (Box 357)
    - Wang (Box 357)
    - Warner-Lambert (Box 357)
    - Weight Watchers International (Box 357)
    - Wells Fargo (Box 357)
    - Western Bancorporation (Box 357)
    - West. International Hotels (Box 357)
    - Westinghouse (Box 357)
    - Westvaco (Box 357)
    - Weyerhauser (Box 357)
    - Whitaker Corporation (Box 357)
    - Wheeling-Pittsburg Steel Corp. (Box 357)
    - White Motor Corp. (Box 357)
    - White Motors (Box 357)
    - White, Weld & Co. (Box 357)
    - Willie Daniels Group (Box 357)
    - Wimpy South Africa (Box 357)
    - Wire Industries (Box 357)
    - Woolworth's (Box 357)
    - W.R. Grace & Co. (Box 357)
  - "X" (Box 357)
    - (Rank) Xerox Corporation (Box 357)
    - Xhosa Development Corporation (Box 357)
  - "Y" (Box 357)
  - "Z" (Box 357)
    - Zapata Corp. (Houston) (Box 357)
    - Zarkinga Enterprises (Box 357)
    - Zinc Corporation Limited (Box 357)
- Lobbyists (Box 357)
  - American Expressions: UNITA (Box 358)
  - B & C International, Inc.: Nigeria (Box 358)
  - Richard Anthony Baenen: Angola (Box 358)
  - Baskin & Sears (see file on John Sears) (Box 358)
    - Reference (Box 358)
    - South Africa, 1983-1985 (Box 358)
  - Black, Manafort, Stone & Kelly (Box 358)
    - other countries, but including Nigeria (Box 358)
      - Somalia, 1988 (Box 358)
      - UNITA, thru 1985, 1986, 1988, (3 folders) (Box 358)
  - Thomas A. Bolan: South Africa (Box 358)
  - Burns and Jacoby: SWA/ (Namibia) (Box 358)
  - Jeremias K. Chitunda: UNITA (Angdon) (Box 358)
  - DGA International, Inc. (Box 358)
    - France 1976-1977, Germany (Box 358)
    - Morocco, 1978-1980 (Box 358)
  - Edelman International Corp.: Morocco, Liberia (Box 358)
  - Foreign Agents: Nael El-Assad (Zaire) (Box 358)
  - Walter E. Fauntroy & Associates (Box 358)
  - Fenton Communications, Inc. (Box 358)
    - Angola, 1986-1989 (Box 358)
  - Freeman, Levy, Kroll & Simonds, SA (Chamber of Mines) (Box 358)
  - Garrett & Company: Republic of Congo (Box 358)
  - Ginsburg, Feldman, Weil, & Bress: Morocco (Box 358)
  - Global USA, Inc.: Bophuthaswana (Box 358)
  - Gold and Liebengood, Inc., Intergold, SA (Box 358)
  - Government Relations, International, Inc., (Free Angola Info. Service--Unita) (Box 358)
  - Graham & James: Cape Verde, 1989 (Box 358)
  - Gray & Co. Public Communications International (Box 358)
    - Angola (Box 358)
    - Morocco, 1985-1986, (2 folders) (Box 358)
    - Reference (Box 358)
  - Griffin Communications, Free Angola Info. Service (Unita) (Box 359)
  - Dr. Lorna Hahn, Inkatha (Box 359)
  - Hampton-Windsor Corp.: Gabon & Zaire (Box 359)
  - Philip Hare, South Africa (see also John Sears) (Box 359)
  - Bill Hecht and Associates: South Africa (Box 359)
  - Hill and Knowlton, Inc.: Morocco (Box 359)
  - Immobiliaria Caribe Y Pacifico, SA: FNLA (Box 359)
  - International Public Affairs Consultants--South Africa (Box 359)
  - Donald G. Johnson Co.: Ciskei (Box 359)
  - Ophelia Jatta: Mozambique (Box 359)
  - Robert A. Kilmarx: SA (textile industry) (Box 359)
  - Kirkpatrick, Lockhart, Johnson: SA, Krugerrands (Box 359)
  - Paul K. Koerner: Unita (Box 359)
  - Laxalt, Washington, Perito & Dubuc: Angola, Nigeria (Box 359)
  - Boaventura Lemane: Renamo (Box 359)
  - Ngqondi L. Masimini: Transkei (Box 359)
  - John P. McGoff: South Africa (Box 359)
  - Clarence V. McKee: Unita (Box 359)
  - Mitchell, Friedlander & Gittleman: Liberia, 1989 (Box 359)
  - Gary Russell Morgan: Ciskei (Box 359)
  - Moroccan National Tourist Office (Box 359)
  - US--Namibia/ SW Africa, 1981, 1984-1985, (3 folders) (Box 359)
    - Trade & Culture, 1982-1983 (Box 359)
    - US--SWA/Namibia Trade and Cul. Council (Box 359)
    - Psycho-Comm and Burns & Jacoby (Box 359)
  - Namibia (SWA/Namibia), Reference (Box 359)
  - NAP International, Inc.: UNITA (Box 359)
  - NM International, Inc.: UNITA (Box 359)
  - North American Precis Syndicate: Morocco (Box 359)
  - Jay Parker & Associates: Venda/ SA (Box 359)
  - Patrick and Associates: South African UN Mission (Box 359)
  - Pearson & Pipkin, Inc.: Embassy of South Africa (Box 359)
  - Plaia Schaumberg & deKieffer: Ciskei (Box 359)
  - Potomac International Corp.: Portugal (OCP) (Box 359)
  - Public Serivice Audience Planners: SA--Embassy--Tourism? (Box 359)
  - Riley & Fox, Inc.: South Africa (Box 360)
  - John D. Sassi: Angola, 1987-1988 (Box 360)
  - Barry Schochet, P.C.: UNITA (Box 360)
  - John Sears: South Africa, 1981, 1985-87, (3 folders) (Box 360)
  - Luis B. Serapiao/ Schaal: Renamo (Box 360)
  - Stuart Spencer: South Africa (Box 360)
  - Smathers & Symington (Box 360)
  - Smathers, Symington & Herlong: (Box 360)
    - South Africa, 1980-1983, 1984-1985, (2 folders) (Box 360)
  - South/North Development Group, Ltd.: People's Republic of Angola (Box 360)
  - (Stu) Spencer, Roberts & Associates, Inc.: South Africa (SWA) (Box 360)
  - Jack Summers: Namibia (NDC) (Box 360)
  - SWAPO--UN, 1964-1980, (4 folders) (Box 360)
    - Obeserver Mission to UN (Box 360)
  - TKC International, Inc., UNITA, 1986 (Box 360)
  - Kenneth Howard Towsey: Transkei (Box 360)
  - Trade Management International, Inc.: Mozambique (Box 360)
  - Transkei Wash. Bureau (Box 360)
  - van Kloberg & Associates (Box 360)
  - Kenneth Watson: SA (Krugerrands) (Box 360)
  - Foreign Agents: Weaver (Box 360)
  - White and Case: Morocco, Gabon, Zaire, Guineau (Box 360)
  - Black, Manafort, Stone & Kelly: UNITA, 1987 (Box 360)
  - Congress: Federal Election Committee Data (Box 361)
  - Congress: Honoraria (Box 361)
  - Neill and Company, Inc.: Cote d'Ivoire (Box 361)
  - The Evans Group, Ltd.: Nigeria (Box 361)
  - Financial Disclosure Forms (Box 361)
  - David Apter & Associates, Inc.: Togo, 1980-1989 (Box 361)
  - The Hannaford Company: The Republic of Congo (Box 361)
  - vonKloberg & Associates: Nigeria, 1989, Zaire, Lesotho, Suriname, etc. (Box 361)
- Preliminary Container List For Accession 1997-0086 (Box 361)
  - Unsorted Clippings, 1970s (Box 1)
  - Filed Clippings, 1960s-1970s (Box 2)
    - Namibia (Box 2)
  - Unsorted Clippings, 1970s (Box 3)
  - Unsorted Clippings, 1970s (Box 4)
  - Journals, 1970s (Box 4)
  - Unsorted Clippings, 1960s-1970s (Box 5)
  - Unsorted Clippings, 1960s-1970s (Box 6)
  - Filed Clippings, 1960s-1970s (Box 7)
    - Zimbabwe, Angola, Mozambique (Box 7)
  - Filed Clippings, 1974-1975 (Box 8)
    - Portugal (Box 8)
  - Filed Clippings, 1960s-1970s (Box 9)
    - Mozambique (Box 9)
  - Journals (Box 9)
    - Africa Today, Special Issues (Box 9)
  - Unsorted Clippings, 1970s (Box 10)
  - Unsorted Clippings, 1970s (Box 11)
  - Filed Clippings, 1960s-1970s (Box 12)
    - South Africa (Box 12)
    - North African Drought (Box 12)
  - Unsorted Clippings, 1970s (Box 13)
  - Unsorted Clippings, 1970s (Box 14)
  - Newsletters and Journals, 1970s (Box 15)
    - Mozambique, Angola, Namibia, South Africa (Box 15)
  - Filed Clippings, 1960s-1970s (Box 16)
    - U.S. Groups (Box 16)
  - Unsorted Clippings, 1970s (Box 17)
  - Unsorted Clippings, 1970s (Box 18)
  - Filed Clippings, 1980s (Box 19)
    - Lobbyists (Box 19)
  - Filed Clippings, 1980s (Box 20)
    - Lobbyists (Box 20)
  - Filed Clippings, 1980s-1990s (Box 21)
    - U.S. Foreign Relations (Box 21)
    - Europe, Canada, Australia (Box 21)
  - Published Congressional Hearings, 1970s (Box 22)
    - African issues (Box 22)
  - Filed Clippings, 1990s (Box 23)
    - Nigeria (Box 23)